HI, YOU GUYS.
HI.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WELL, IT'S JUST...
IT'S ONE OF THESE
SITUATIONS
THAT I JUST HATE.
YOU KNOW, A MASSAGE CLIENT
GAVE ME THREE TICKETS
TO THE HELMUT PELTZ EXHIBIT
AT THE MORGAN-CHASE MUSEUM.
NOW YOU'RE THINKING
YOU'VE GOT TO SLEEP WITH HIM.
NO. NO, IT'S JUST THAT
HE GAVE ME THREE TICKETS
AND THERE ARE SIX OF US.
I'LL GIVE UP
MY TICKET.
ME, TOO.
OKAY. THAT'S SO GENEROUS.
AND I THINK ROSS
IS GENEROUS, TOO.
GREAT. OKAY,
THEN IT'S JUST US GIRLS.
GREAT.
SO WHAT-WHAT IS
THE EXHIBIT?
IT'S MOSTLY JUST PHOTOGRAPHS
OF, UM, LESBIAN LOVE SCENES
INTERSPERSED WITH VIDEO GAMES
AND FREE SANDWICHES.
OH, MAN...
HEY.
HI THERE.
HEY, ROSS, LISTEN--
CHANDLER GOT YOU OUT OF GOING
TO THE LESBIAN/SANDWICH MUSEUM
THIS WEEKEND.
THANKS, BUT I HAVE PLANS.
UH, ELIZABETH AND I
ARE GOING OUT OF TOWN.
OH, THAT'S GREAT--
THINK ABOUT ALL THE MONEY
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE.
WHY? WHAT?
WELL, HER FATHER PAYS YOU
FOR BABY-SITTING, RIGHT?
NO. THAT'S FUNNY, BUT MAYBE
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON
YOU KNOW, LET IT GO, STOP IT.
BESIDES, RACHEL'S GOING OUT
WITH ELIZABETH'S FATHER
SO, UH, HE'S MUCH
OLDER THAN SHE IS.
LOOKS LIKE I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
INTERESTED IN FOSSILS, HUH?
ROSS, ALL THAT DOES
IS REMIND US
THAT YOU ARE INTERESTED
IN FOSSILS.
OKAY, OKAY.
UH, WELL, UH
RACHEL'S GOING TO NEED TO
YELLSWEET NOTHING'S
IN HIS EAR, HUH?
ROSS...
OH, COME ON,
YOU GUYS
THAT'S FUNNY, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE HE'S GOING TO...
HE'S GOT, LIKE, A HEARING AID,
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE...
OH...
'CAUSE HE'S ALL OLD, YOU KNOW?
( Paul chuckling )
'KAY, LOOK, ROSS...
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
SINCE LIZZIE LIKES
YOU SO MUCH
I'VE DECIDED TO
ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE GOING
OUT WITH HER.
REALLY? THAT...
OKAY, THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH. BUT THEN I
CHANGED MY MIND.
I'M FUNNY LIKE THAT.
SO I'VE TOLD LIZZIE
AND NOW I'M TELLING YOU--
I DON'T WANT YOU SEEING
MY DAUGHTER ANYMORE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I-I REALIZE IT UPSETS YOU...
YES, IT DOES.
BUT... ELIZABETH AND I
ARE BOTH ADULTS
AND SO I DON'T THINK
THERE'S REALLY ANYTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT.
I'LL CALL THE UNIVERSITY
AND TELL THEM ABOUT
YOUR RELATIONSHIP
AND HAVE YOU FIRED.
OH! A MAN WITH A PLAN.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
YOU GET YOUR PICTURE
BACK UP THERE
ON THE WALL OF FAME.
I KNOW.
IT WAS SO COOL
WHEN I WAS UP THERE BEFORE.
ME AND JIM BELUSHI
WOULD BE
CRACKING UP
ABOUT SOMETHING.
THEN I GET FIRED
OFF DAYS OF OUR LIVES
AND HE TAKES ME DOWN.
NOW HE'S JUST
LAUGHING AT ME.
LOOK AT HIM, THAT
SMUG BELUSHI BASTARD.
OH, OKAY, MAYBE WHEN
THEY PUT YOUR PICTURE BACK UP
THEY COULD PUT YOU
NEXT TO MATT LAUER.
LOOK AT HIM JUST
SMILING AT ME.
( giggles )
YEAH, I KNOW,
WE'D BE GREAT TOGETHER.
OH... PSST.
HEY. SO, I'M BACK.
( foreign accent ):
WHO ARE YOU?
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
FROM THE WALL?
OKAY, MAYBE THIS WILL
JOG YOUR MEMORY, HUH?
HUH?
OKAY, ANYWAY, I'M READY
TO GO BACK UP ON THE WALL.
I'M THE STAR
OF A NEW TV SHOW.
SHOW ME IN THE TV BOOK.
WELL, IT'S NOT
ON TV YET.
WELL, THEN IT'S
NOT ON THE WALL YET.
OKAY, FINE.
I WILL BRING YOU A TAPE, HUH?
SO, NOW, DO YOU HAVE
ANY OF MATT LAUER'S CLOTHES
HERE, MAYBE?
JUST ONES THAT HAVEN'T
BEEN CLEANED YET?
I LOVE MUSEUMS.
SOAKING UP ALL THE CULTURE.
YEAH.
WHERE DO YOU WANT
TO START?
OH, THE GIFT SHOP!
YEAH!
HEY, AND THEN LUNCH.
OH, WAIT. YES
BUT I CAN'T EAT TOO MUCH.
PAUL'S TAKING ME OUT
TO DINNER TONIGHT.
HE SAID HE HAS
A BIG SURPRISE PLANNED.
OH, WOW. DO YOU THINK
MAYBE HE'S GOING
TO TELL YOU HE'S GAY?
WHAT? NO. WHY?
NO REASON.
THAT WOULD JUST BE
A REALLY BIG SURPRISE, RIGHT?
YOU CAN PUT THE
AISLE OVER HERE
AND HAVE THE WEDDING
CEREMONY RIGHT OVER HERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD GET
MARRIED HERE.
THIS WOULD BE
A BEAUTIFUL PLACE
TO GET MARRIED.
BUT I WOULDN'T PUT
THE AISLE THERE
AND I WOULD NEVER
HAVE THE CEREMONY THERE.
YOU'D HAVE THE CEREMONY UNDER
THIS BIG BEAUTIFUL ARCH.
MAY I HELP YOU?
OH, SORRY.
DIDN'T MEAN
TO INTERRUPT.
IT'S JUST SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL SPACE.
DO YOU DO A LOT
OF WEDDINGS HERE?
YES, WE'RE VERY POPULAR.
THERE'S A TWO-YEAR
WAITING LIST. SORRY.
MONICA, YOU SHOULD
TOTALLY PUT YOUR NAME DOWN
FOR THIS PLACE.
WHAT? ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'M NOT GETTING MARRIED.
I'M NOT EVEN ENGAGED.
BUT THERE'S A TWO-YEAR WAIT
AND THEN WHAT IF
YOU GET ENGAGED
IN TWO YEARS
AND THEN YOU'VE GOT
TO WAIT ANOTHER TWO
YEARS FOR THIS PLACE?
THAT'S FOUR YEARS.
CHANDLER'S NOT GOING
TO WAIT THAT LONG.
HE'S GOING TO FIND
SOMEBODY ELSE, YOU KNOW?
SOMEONE WHO DID PUT
THEIR NAME
ON THE LIST.
AND IT CAN'T HURT
TO PUT YOUR NAME DOWN.
IF IN TWO YEARS
YOU'RE NOT ENGAGED
YOU JUST DON'T USE IT.
WELL, I GUESS THERE IS NO HARM
IN PUTTING MY NAME DOWN.
I'M GOING
TO DO IT, TOO.
ME, TOO.
REALLY? WHO WOULD
YOU MARRY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T HAVE ANYONE
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW?
OH, PHEEBS.
DON'T FEEL TOO SORRY FOR ME.
AT LEAST MY BOYFRIEND ISN'T GAY.
PHOEBE, THAT'S NOT...
DON'T EVEN GET ME
STARTED ON YOURS.
HEY.
SO, DID YOU WATCH
THE TAPE OF MY SHOW?
I DID.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GET ME
BACK UP THERE.
NO, YOU DON'T GO UP
ON THE WALL.
WHAT?
BUT YOU SAW THE SHOW.
YES. IT WAS VERY OFFENSIVE
TO MY PEOPLE.
DRY CLEANERS?
RUSSIANS. IT SHOWED THEM
AS TERRORISTS AND VILLAINS.
OKAY, OKAY, LOOK
YOU GOT HARRISON FORD
UP THERE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
MR. FORD IS
A VERY GOOD CUSTOMER.
HE BRINGS US A LOT OF CLOTHES.
YOU BRING US NOTHING.
OKAY, WELL, THAT MAY BE TRUE
BUT IN AIR FORCE ONE, OKAY,
THE RUSSIANS WERE TERRORISTS
AND EVIL, AND PLUS HE KILLS
A BUNCH OF THEM.
THAT'S OFFENSIVE TO RUSSIANS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN IT.
OH, YOU SHOULD. IT'S GREAT.
THIS PLACE IS REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN COMING HERE
SINCE I WAS A KID.
THIS USED TO BE MY GRANDMA'S.
WOW. THE ONLY THING I GOT
FROM MY GRANDMOTHER
WAS HER EYES.
I MEAN, NOT HER ACTUAL
EYEBALLS
BUT PEOPLE SAY
THAT MY EYES...
DO YOU WANT TO MAKE OUT?
SURE.
MM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT YOUR FATHER.
WELL, WHATEVER
WORKS FOR YOU.
NO, NO. UH...
HE JUST REALLY
FREAKED ME OUT BEFORE.
OH. WELL, SO WE HAVE
TO HIDE OUR RELATIONSHIP
FROM ONE MORE PERSON,
BIG DEAL.
BESIDES, WE'VE HAD
FUN HIDING IT.
YEAH.
MM.
HEY, UM, YOU BROUGHT
PROTECTION, RIGHT?
WHY? ARE THERE, LIKE,
BEARS OR SOMETHING?
NO.
OH. OH!
OH, PROTECTION.
NO, YEAH.
NO, THAT-THAT I FORGOT.
I'LL JUST RUN TO
THE STORE AND GET SOME.
NO, HEY, HEY,
I'M THE GUY.
I'LL GET IT.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
THE STORE IS?
NO.
DO YOU WANT TO RIDE
AROUND TOWN
ON MY LITTLE PINK BICYCLE?
A LITTLE BIT.
[LAUGHS]
I'LL BE BACK
IN TEN MINUTES.
OKAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GET
IN THE HOT TUB
AND I'LL MEET YOU THERE?
OKAY.
( door opens )
Rachel:
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT A GREAT SURPRISE.
THIS IS SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE.
Paul:
THANK YOU. IT USED
TO BE MY MOTHER'S.
THIS IS THE KITCHEN.
( phone rings )
Chandler:
You've reached Monica
and Chandler's.
If you're listening
to this message,
we're probably screening.
YEAH, WE ARE.
( machine beeps )
Hi. This is Hildy
from the Morgan-Chase museum.
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
I want to let her know
that there was a cancellation
and if she's still interested
in having the Bing-Geller
wedding in our facility
it is available...
THIS IS CHANDLER BING!
YES, THE GROOM.
NO, NOT THE GROOM!
SO SECLUDED
UP HERE.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I LIKE IT HERE.
MM-HMM. I FEEL
LIKE WE'RE
THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
IN THE WORLD.
WHOOPS.
SORRY.
( gasps )
WHAT'S THE MATTER, HONEY?
DID YOU SEE A LITTLE MOUSE?
NO, NO. BIG BEAR.
BIG BEAR OUTSIDE.
I THOUGHT I HEARD A BEAR.
WOULD YOU GO
CHECK ON THAT?
HONEY, WE DON'T HAVE
ANY BEARS HERE.
WELL, OKAY.
W-WOULD YOU GET
ME A DIET COKE?
OKAY.
BE RIGHT BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME WITH PAUL.
YEAH, I RECOGNIZE
THE ANKLES.
GET OUT. GET OUT.
HERE YOU GO, HONEY.
OH, THANK YOU.
DIET COKE.
OH... ICE.
I NEED ICE.
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
YOU AND YOUR ICE.
OH! GET OUT!
GET OUT, GO. COME ON.
QUICK.
NO, NOT IN THERE.
NOT IN THERE.
HE'S IN THERE.
DID YOU REALLY
HEAR A BEAR?
GO!
HERE YOU GO, HONEY.
OH!
ONE DIET COKE
WITH ICE.
OH, THANK YOU.
I AM... SO HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE HERE.
HERE I AM!
ELIZABETH!
OH, LOOK!
ELIZABETH'S HERE!
WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
YOU GUYS?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WE WERE HERE?
UM...
WELL, SHE OBVIOUSLY
SAW THE TIRE TRACKS
THAT WERE LEADING UP
TO THE CLOSED GARAGE.
OBVIOUSLY.
ELIZABETH...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
DID-DID-DID YOU
COME UP HERE
TO WORK ON THAT TERM
PAPER OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, WHY DON'T
YOU, YOU KNOW
GO IN THAT ROOM AND
DO YOUR HOMEWORK?
OH, I WOULDN'T DO IT
IN THERE, UM
THAT'S MY DAD'S BEDROOM.
THAT'S YOUR...
THAT'S YOUR
DAD'S BEDROOM.
( loudly ):
THAT'S YOUR
DAD'S BEDROOM!
HO-HO!
WHY ARE YOU YELLING,
RACHEL?
THAT DIET COKE, I THINK--
JUST STRAIGHT TO MY HEAD.
WHOO!
HI, HONEY.
SEE YA LATER.
WHAT, I-I BOUGHT
GROCERIES.
I WAS GOING TO MAKE YOU DINNER.
WELL, NEXT TIME, ASK.
OR, AT LEAST,
WAIT FOR ME TO ASK.
( beeps )
Hi, this is Hildy
from the Morgan-Chase Museum.
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
OH, NO.
I want to let her know
that there was a cancellation
and if she's still interested
in having
the Bing-Geller wedding
in our facility...
OH, PLEASE.
OH, PLEASE,
HE DIDN'T HEAR IT.
HE DIDN'T HEAR IT!
This is Chandler Bing!
NO!
CAN I HELP YOU?
UH... YEAH. WHERE'S THE GUY
WHO DECIDES WHOSE PICTURES
GO UP ON THE WALL?
HE'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
OH, YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
ALL RIGHT, MAKE SURE YOU
TELL HIM THAT JOEY TRIBBIANI
STOPPED BY TO DROP OFF
ALL THESE CLOTHES. I'M AN ACTOR.
I'M TRYING TO GET MY PICTURE
UP THERE ON THE WALL.
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE TWO PEOPLE
WHO COULD GET YOUR PICTURE
UP THERE.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, MAYBE YOU AND I
GO OUT FOR DRINKS.
YOU'RE THE OTHER ONE,
RIGHT?
SO, LIZZIE, ARE YOU
PLANNING ON STAYING THE NIGHT?
OH, NO, NO.
BELIEVE ME, I'M LEAVING
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
GOOD. GOOD.
NOT THAT WE DON'T
WANT YOU TO STAY.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE WELCOME.
HOW MUCH MORE HOMEWORK
DO YOU HAVE?
UH, I JUST HAVE ONE PROBLEM LEFT
THAT I DO NOT KNOW HOW TO SOLVE.
UH, RACHEL,
MAYBE YOU WANT TO COME UPSTAIRS
AND HELP ME FIGURE IT OUT?
( shaky ):
REALLY?
OKAY.
OKAY, I-I'LL
GO UPSTAIRS...
IF-IF YOU... GET ME
SOMETHING FROM THE CAR.
WHAT DO YOU NEED
FROM THE CAR?
SURPRISE ME.
( yelling ):
SO, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
IN THE CAR
I WILL BE UPSTAIRS
AND THAT'S WHERE EVERYBODY'S
GOING TO BE!
( heavy sigh )
JUST RELAX, JUST RELAX.
PAUL, YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
SHE LIKES YOU.
SHE...
I THINK SHE LIKES YOU.
SHE LIKES YOU.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A...
NEAT GUY.
YOU ARE THE MAN.
YOU ARE THE MAN!
STILL GOT IT.
( inhaling )
STILL SEXY.
YOU'RE JUST A LOVE MACHINE.
( high-pitched ):
♪ I'M JUST A LOVE MACHINE ♪
♪ AND I DON'T WORK
FOR NOBODY BUT YOU ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY, HUH! ♪
( roaring )
SHOW TIME.
♪ I'M JUST A LOVE MACHINE ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY! ♪
♪ HUH! ♪
PHOEBE...
YEAH?
HAVE YOU SEEN
CHANDLER?
NO, WHY?
THE WOMAN FROM
THE MUSEUM CALLED
AND SAID THAT THERE
WAS A CANCELLATION
AND THAT WE COULD
MOVE UP OUR WEDDING
AND CHANDLER HEARD.
( gasps )
I KNOW.
HOW BAD IS THIS?
WELL, WITH A REGULAR GUY,
IT'S BAD.
WITH CHANDLER--
OH, DEAR GOD!
I KNOW, I KNOW.
AND HE TOTALLY
FREAKED OUT
AND I CAN'T FIND
HIM ANYWHERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
I'M NEVER GOING
TO LISTEN TO YOU AGAIN
THAT'S FOR SURE.
( whiny ):
AND WHAT HARM CAN IT DO
IF YOU JUST PUT YOUR NAME DOWN?
RACHEL SAID THAT.
WELL, RACHEL'S NOT HERE!
OH, HERE IT IS!
OOH, JOEY, WHY DID YOU SIGN IT
"SON OF A BITCH"?
I DIDN'T DO THAT.
WHO WOULD'VE DONE THAT?
SON OF A BITCH!
OKAY, MAYBE ASK THIS GUY.
YOU--
GET OUT OF MY SHOP!
WHAT DID HE DO?
HE WENT OUT WITH MY WIFE!
JOEY!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HEY, I DID NOT GO OUT
WITH YOUR WIFE, OKAY?
I WENT OUT WITH HER.
THAT'S MY WIFE!
GET OUT!
( yelling in Russian )
WELL, WE SHOULD GO.
YEAH.
ROSS?
ELIZABETH.
OKAY... OKAY...
I'M GOING TO GO
OUT THIS WINDOW.
I'LL MEET YOU AT
THE FRONT DOOR.
TELL THEM YOU'RE
GOING HOME, OKAY?
OKAY.
Rachel:
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
NO, DON'T GO
IN THERE!
DON'T GO
I NEED
ANOTHER SODA.
ROSS!
OH, MY GOD! ROSS!
WHAT IN HEAVEN'S NAME
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AND THAT IS WHY
WE CANNOT SEE EACH
OTHER ANYMORE.
ROSS...
YOU AND I ARE GOING TO HAVE
TO HAVE A LITTLE TALK.
DADDY, UH...
YOU'RE NEXT!
OKAY. I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS HERE.
LET ME JUST SEE
IF I GOT THIS STRAIGHT.
I TELL YOU TO STAY AWAY
FROM MY DAUGHTER
OR I'LL HAVE YOU FIRED.
WHAT YOU HEARD WAS:
"TAKE MY DAUGHTER,
COME UP TO MY COUNTRY HOUSE
AND RUIN MY WEEKEND
WITH RACHEL."
OKAY, PLEASE, PLEASE, PAUL.
JUST LET ME EXPLAIN...
NO, LET ME EXPLAIN!
FIRED!
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
HAVE ME FIRED.
BUT, UH, I WANT
YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU AND I ARE NOT
ALL THAT DIFFERENT.
I MEAN...
I, TOO, AM A NEAT GUY.
WHAT?
AND I, TOO
AM JUST A
LOVE MACHINE.
( humming "Love Machine" )
( grunts )
ROSS...
LET ME SHOW YOU
WHERE THE GUEST ROOM IS.
I'M SO SORRY.
PLEASE STOP
FREAKING OUT.
I'M NOT FREAKING OUT.
WHY WOULD I BE FREAKING OUT?
A WOMAN NAMED HILDY CALLED
TO SAY WE WERE GETTING MARRIED
BUT THAT HAPPENS EVERY DAY.
WAH-AHHH-AHHH!
HONEY, WE WERE
AT THIS BEAUTIFUL PLACE
AND I JUST PUT OUR NAMES DOWN
FOR FUN.
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE HARM
IN THAT?
RIGHT HERE.
( clucking )
CHANDLER, PLEASE DON'T THINK
I WAS TRYING TO PRESSURE YOU.
PHOEBE AND RACHEL
JUST THOUGHT THAT...
PHOEBE AND RACHEL...
SO THE PEOPLE THAT KNEW
ABOUT OUR WEDDING BEFORE ME
WERE YOU, PHOEBE AND RACHEL
HILDY, AND APPARENTLY
SOME BAND
CALLED THE STARLIGHT
MAGIC SEVEN
WHO ARE AVAILABLE,
BY THE WAY.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
PLEASE DON'T TAKE THIS
TO MEAN ANYTHING
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T.
OKAY.
REALLY?
YES, IF IT REALLY
DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING
BECAUSE YOU KNOW THAT
I'M JUST NOT READY...
I KNOW.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW I'M GOING TO GO TELL JOEY
THAT YOU'RE BACK.
HE WAS REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
HEY, DID SHE BUY IT?
TOTALLY.
SO DID HILDY SHOW YOU THE PLACE?
YEAH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE GOING
TO ASK MONICA TO MARRY YOU.
I KNOW.
HEY, GUNTHER.
TAKE THESE CAPPUCCINOS
TO TABLE ELEVEN
AND THAT GUY OVER THERE
WANTS SOME BISCOTTI.
OH, UH, WELL, I JUST,
ACTUALLY, CAME IN
FOR A CUP OF
COFFEE TO GO.
DO YOU STILL WORK HERE?
NO, NO, I QUIT A LONG TIME AGO.
DID I FORGET TO TELL YOU THAT?
I'M SORRY.
NO, THAT'S COOL.
I WAS GOING TO FIRE YOU ANYWAY.
GREAT!